Hello everyone, before this course begins, let me introduce you to CLO Ecosystem.
CLO Ecosystem is the ecosystem of CLO.
CLO Virtual Fashion Company is creating a new ecosystem for digital fashion.
Through the integration of clothing design software such as CLO, Marvelous Designer and Genie, and Closet and Connect, we focus on the content of the clothing platform,
deeply involved in clothing from design development to production and promotion of the entire process.
To build an efficient and sustainable workflow.
In this video, I will explain the basic concepts of CLO, Closet and Connect,
and describe its basic workflow, and show their applications in the process.
First, I will explain what CLO is, and what its main function is.
CLO is a software based on 3D clothing sewing technology.
It provides efficient virtual clothing solution by digitalizing clothing design, production and marketing, and so on.
By using CLO, users can maximize their creativity,
improve productivity,
and increase their productivity.
This plays an important role in the digital transformation of the clothing industry.
Next, I will introduce the main functions of CLO.
One of the main functions of CLO is to be able to make clothes in real time,
and can quickly and accurately achieve the design structure of the clothing effect,
and can react in real time to change the fabric,
and adjust the effect after the clothing version.
In addition, in the design stage,
CLO can effectively adjust the design of clothing color and style,
and create 3D clothing samples to replace real samples,
thereby saving production time and cost.
Finally, the 3D clothing created in CLO can be applied in various fields,
such as electronic business content,
and provide more possibilities for digital clothing creation applications.
Next is Closet.
Closet is a cloud-based platform.
You can upload and manage your 3D assets here,
and can share and communicate with internal and external teams.
One of the main functions of Closet is to be able to use multi-layer file structure.
This structure can be more efficient in file management.
You can set the corresponding layer structure according to the needs of different organizations,
such as companies, brands, product lines, developers, and studios,
and manage and share your 3D resources in different layers.
In addition, you can also store digital assets in Closet,
upload various file formats,
in addition to the 3D file format shown in the picture,
including documents such as DXF, Adobe Illustrator, Excel, and PDF.
Closet is also a platform that is easy to communicate with.
In the process of style design, color modification, and other suggestions,
you can share your thoughts with the internal or external team on the platform,
communicate with each other, and obtain more accurate and timely feedback.
Finally, by using various tools such as online process list and material list,
you can systematically manage the entire production process of the product,
and achieve efficient workflow.
The following is a description of the concept of Closet.
Closet is a face-to-face global user,
digital fashion community and online mall.
Creators can communicate with each other on the platform,
users can also upload their works here,
display and sell,
and the face-to-face supplier will also upload their digitalized products here.
First of all, in the shop category,
you can easily obtain all the materials needed for digital clothing creation,
and you can also use the 3D resources created by Closet to make a profit.
The work wall is a display.
The creator can share inspiration here using the space of the work created by Closet.
This promotes active communication between users,
and creates an environment full of creativity.
The competition is regularly held by fashion brands and Closet.
The space for the competition is only to provide the creators with opportunities to show themselves,
and participate in the innovation of the digital fashion industry.
Designers can gain industry recognition through the competition,
expand their career path,
and make contributions to the development of digital fashion.
In the application section,
there are various functions included.
First is Everywhere.
It is a tool bag,
which can be automatically optimized for games,
entertainment and virtual space and other digital space clothing.
Next is LiveSync.
It can quickly and conveniently connect Closet and Unreal Engine,
allowing users to directly import the clothing and materials created in Closet into Unreal Engine.
This allows them to use various Unreal resources,
including MetaHuman.
Next is AR.
This function allows users to convert the clothing created,
into an AR filter,
to achieve a more diversified use.
Next is Genie.
This is a free software.
Even without professional clothing design knowledge,
users can easily carry out digital clothing design.
Genie provides a convenient tool for non-clothing professionals,
allowing users to quickly,
easily,
and enjoy creative pleasure.
Finally is Gamewear.
Gamewear is designed for creators and players,
allowing digital fashion designers to upload and share.
For customized clothing after the optimization of various games,
whether you are the creator of the latest design,
or a player who pursues the unique character style required for the game,
you can find it in Gamewear.
It combines creativity and fashion perfectly.
The above has introduced the overall concept and main functions of Closet and Connect.
Now let's go through Closet's basic workflow video,
to learn more about how to use these tools in the actual clothing production process,
First is the inspiration creation stage.
You can use Closet's visualized design version to create an inspiration version.
Then, in the Connect process,
get resources that are in line with the design inspiration,
as reference materials,
such as fabric,
fabric,
and other design assets that are in line with the design inspiration.
Next, you can plan your design in Closet.
If you have a favorite or popular online clothing style,
you can import it into Closet,
and organize the product list of all styles,
which is easy to check,
and then enter the design creation stage.
At this stage,
you can use the online style to modify the color scheme.
You can also redesign from the basic version.
The final design effect can also be uploaded to Closet,
and shared and communicated with your partners.
In Closet,
you can use the current 3D clothing preview effect
to give feedback on clothing modifications,
or you can also receive the modification suggestions given by your partners,
and check the design feedback.
After receiving the feedback,
you can upload it to Closet,
and modify it in Closet.
After the modification is completed,
you can upload it to Closet again,
and do a second inspection,
and then determine the final design plan.
After the final plan is confirmed,
you can integrate the entire series of styles,
and select them in Closet,
whether to use them or not.
Then, you can further improve the clothing styles used,
and then check the final product line style.
When you enter the listing stage,
you can add further information to Closet
for the clothing styles that will eventually enter the production stage.
For example, you can add the size information of the clothing,
code, etc.,
and mark information such as paper sample, etc.
You can also arrange the clothing,
and the material list for the production cost.
You can ensure that all the preparation work needed in the production process
can be successfully completed.
You can share the file again to Closet,
and you can check the supply list online.
There are also many ways to promote the finished clothing in the market.
You can upload it to Connect,
and share it with others,
communicate or sell it.
In addition, you can use the various services
that we just mentioned,
such as wearable equipment
and enhance real-time technology,
and let the design enter the virtual universe.
You can use 3D clothing in various industries,
such as games,
the original universe,
and so on.
In addition,
you can use Closet,
which is the most advanced technology in the market.
Closet and Connect have participated in every stage like this.
From concept construction to final sales and expansion,
it makes the whole process seamless.